This is made on Abhishek's
lyrics blender ′
You can use any font
Apply any music
OR
song
Change background image
as your choice
Let me show you
An example
music-AlonePt2
.srt taken from
RentAnAdviser.com
font-Akronim
taken from
font.google.com
background - nature,water
taken from
source unsplash
Made By -
Abhishek verma
We were young
Posters on the wall
Praying We are the ones
That the teacher
wouldn't call
We would stare at
each other
'Cause we were
always in trouble
And all the cool kids
Did their own thing
I was on the outside
Always looking in
Yeah‚ I was there
but I wasn't
They never really cared
if I wasn't
We all need that someone
Who gets you
like no one else
Right when you
need it the most
We all need
a soul to rely on
A shoulder to
cry on
A friend through the
highs and the lows
I am not gonna
make it alone
La la la la la la
La la la la la
–lone
I am not gona make it
alone
La la la la la la
La la la la la
–lone
I am not gonna
make it alone
La la la la la la
La la la la la
–lone
I am not gona make it
alone
La la la la la la
La la la la la
–lone
Then I saw your face
Your forgiving eyes
Looking back at me
From the other side
Like you understood me
And I am never
letting you go‚ oh
We all need
that someone
Who gets you like
no one else
Right when you
need it the most
We all need a soul
to rely on
A shoulder
to cry on
A friend through
the highs and the lows
I am not gonna make it
alone
La la la la la la
La la la la la
–lone
I am not gona make it
alone
La la la la la la
La la la la la
–lone
I am not gona make it
alone
La la la la la la
La la la la la
–lone
I am not gona make it
alone
La la la la la la
La la la la la
–lone
I am not gona make it
alone
La la la la la la
–lone
I am not gona make it
alone
La la la la la la
La la la la la
–lone
'Cause you are
that someone
That gets me like
no one else
Right when I need
it the most
And I will be
the one you rely on
Your shoulder
to cry on
A friend through
the highs and the lows
I am not gona
make it alone
La la la la la la
–lone
I am not gona
make it alone
La la la la la la
–lone
I am not gona make it
alone
La la la la la la
–lone
I am not gona make it alone
La la la la la la
–lone
I am not gona
make it alone
THANKS FOR WATCHING